There is a woman over there, a little child died mistakenly.
The child was sick and you went to a local chemist to buy some tablets.
These tablets resulted to death and the thing became a controversy.
and the Lord saved you out of it.
Later, you left the place.
I'm telling you, you are facing the spirit of death.
You keep seeing this child and some dead people in your dream.
A light in complexion woman, tall, stand up among the newcomers.
The SCOAN Service
The man of God said the woman he is referring to is among the newcomers.
You can see - this is the newcomers' section.
The Book of 2 Peter 1:21 says, for prophecy never had its origin in the will of man
but men spoke from God as they were carried along by the Holy Spirit.
No, that is for Jesus!
That is for Jesus!
The SCOAN Service
That is for Jesus! Thank You, Jesus!
Thank You for the revelation!
This is for Jesus!
Thank You, Jesus!
Thank You for the revelation!
I am a servant and I am sent to deliver you.
The SCOAN Service
Let's listen to Mrs Gloria Okhae as she testifies to the goodness of God in her life.
I am Gloria Okhae.
I am from Edo State.
I came to Lagos because I was pursued by forces of death.
I came and met my sister - she stays in Lagos here.
I told her about my problem.
I told my sister how I see death.
She asked, "Is it when you are sleeping?"; I said, "No".
I said, "As I am talking to you now, I can see them. They are surrounding me.
I also hear strange voices telling me that my time is up.
In my dream, I saw this man of God; I have never met him before.
I told my sister, "I want to visit The SCOAN".
One of her sons brought me here. That was my first time.
I came with a catalogue of problems.
I don't even know where to start from because what I'm seeing is unusual.
It is abnormal.
Nobody sees it; only me.
I came to The SCOAN and I was sitting among the newcomers.
Suddenly, there was a prophecy that described my situation.
There is a woman over there, a little child died mistakenly.
The child was sick and you went to a local chemist to buy some tablets.
These tablets resulted to death and the thing became a controversy.
and the Lord saved you out of it.
Later, you left the place.
I'm telling you, you are facing the spirit of death.
You keep seeing this child and some dead people in your dream.
A light in complexion woman, tall, stand up among the newcomers.
The SCOAN Service
The man of God said the woman he is referring to is among the newcomers.
You can see - this is the newcomers' section.
The SCOAN Service
He said, "There is a woman here, you are fair in complexion and tall".
Some time ago, you went to a local chemist to purchase
some tablets for a little child that died mistakenly through you".
The prophecy referred to me; it described my situation.
He went further to say that ever since then,
I have been faced with the spirit of death.
I came out to confirm the prophecy because it described my situation.
What the man of God said was actually true.
The child in question was my husband's son.
He fell sick so I ran to a local chemist to buy some tablets.
I never knew that the drugs were fake.
A few hours later, this child died and I was accused.
There was a commotion. That eventually sent me out of my matrimonial home.
After some time, I was being confronted with death.
I kept seeing this child in my dream and some other dead people.
When I go to the market, what I see is death.
When I'm in the house, death.
When I'm eating, death. When I'm in the bathroom, death.
I keep seeing dead people.
Even when I'm in the car, the people in the car will suddenly turn into dead people.
It has been a life of living among the dead.
Do you mean you see them physically?
Yes
How do they look like?
They look like normal human beings but I know that they are dead.
How do you know that they are dead?
Because they are familiar dead people that I know are dead.
The SCOAN Service
When I'm in the market and want to buy something from somebody,
before I get there, the person might be looking normal.
but suddenly the person will just change into a dead person I know.
Then, I will leave.
I will not be able to buy what I wanted to buy.
If I want to eat, I will see dead people who want to eat with me,
then I will be afraid; I will not eat.
So, I was growing skinny.
The moment they appear, I will drop the food.
Why?
I don't want to eat with the dead.
The SCOAN Service
Can you remember the very day you started seeing these people?
It started in the dream.
- In the dream?
- Yes.
When I see dead people in my dream and wake up, I would say, "This dream, I bind you!"
I would begin to bind.
I would say, "Thank God it is a dream".
But very soon, I would now see them in the physical.
What of that child that died?
I was seeing him and some other dead people.
They would show me time and tell me that my time is up.
When I entered a vehicle, the people would be normal people.
But as soon as I sat down and looked again, I saw dead people.
As I was coming here, they were following me.
But when they got to the gate, they could not enter.
The SCOAN Service
When I was delivered last Sunday, I said, "Let me put my faith to test".
I went to the shop in the church.
I asked the woman to give me some snacks and a soft drink.
I came inside the church; I took it.
I was watching to see whether there would be any negative reaction.
I didn't see dead people.
The SCOAN Service
I went home; I was happy.
Then I told my sister about it.
"Maybe it was because I was inside the church.
So get me my food and let me see if there will be some faces."
I put my food down; I was watching because they would normally come.
In fact, death was haunting me.
I was dying and nobody could understand me.
One doctor told me that my case was beyond medical intervention.
Then another woman told me that I needed crusade anointing to get out of this problem.
I put my food down and was watching to see if there was any reaction.
I didn't see anything.
The SCOAN Service
So, I ate my meal.
When it was time to sleep - the dead people would normally come
and say, "There will be no sleep for you; it is death!"
I lay down; I slept for the first time in my life for many years.
I slept. In fact, I didn't turn.
My sister said that she came to see whether I was sleeping.
She discovered that I was sleeping.
In fact, I slept.
Since the deliverance, it has been a life of glorious liberty.
No more death!
Amen!
Jesus Christ has set Mrs Gloria free from the spirit of death.
The problem had tormented her for many years.
When your problem has advanced beyond the power of nature, it has become a curse.
Now, who else can remove a curse except God?
Who else can justly deliver?
It is none other than our Lord Jesus Christ.
RV: Mel Flowers 02/04/2019